[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110701pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "NN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "PRP", ",", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "NNS", "WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 30, "question": "How have they got themselves, do you think, into that position?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 31, "answer": "Well, I'm not sort of privy to it, but the producers who have been involved with it are mainly people who come from rock.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110701pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 42, "question": "From a musical perspective, how did you rate it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "NN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 43, "answer": "Well, I'm not a critic, and I never talk about other people's work.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110701pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 53, "question": "Is the narrative key, do you think, to longevity on these things?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "TO", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 54, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["London"]}, "docId": "110701pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "IN", "``", "NNP", "''", "VBN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ":", "``", "NNP", "''", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", ",", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 63, "question": "Have you had a situation like they've got where it opens and the criticism's pretty heavy, everyone's saying this isn't going to survive, and then it's gone on to be a huge hit?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "CC", "DT", "NN", "POS", "RB", "JJ", ",", "NN", "POS", "VBG", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", ",", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 64, "answer": "Yes, I think -- although \"Evita\" been a very big hit in London -- \"Evita\" when it opened it here, had pretty bad reviews.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110701pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 74, "question": "How much have the critics got to you over the years?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 75, "answer": "I don't really care very much if I don't think that the critics really understand music.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110701pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "NN", "CC", "NN", ",", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 76, "question": "But if it's someone, though, that you respect, what is the most hurtful kind of thing they could say that would really get to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", ",", "IN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 77, "answer": "Well, I guess if it's somebody who I did respect as a musician said that the score was humdrum or something, then I would be sad if I believed in the score.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Britain"]}, "docId": "110701pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 87, "question": "What do you think it is?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 88, "answer": "Well, I think the television -- and I've been involved with the television casting programs in Britain.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110701pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 97, "question": "Can they produce genuine, bona fide stars, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "NN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 98, "answer": "Yes, of course they can.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Susan Boyle"]}, "docId": "110701pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ":", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "DT", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NN", ",", "CC", "CD", "IN", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "DT", "JJ", ",", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "``", "NNPS", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 109, "question": "When you watch a Susan Boyle, for example, what do you think of someone like her?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 110, "answer": "Susan Boyle -- of course, we all know, it was an extraordinary moment, not just in television, but one of the most extraordinary things that ever happened to a musical, because talk about something out of the blue for \"Les Miserables.\"", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Susan Boyle"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110701pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 134, "question": "You're not doing that anymore, are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "JJR", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 135, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110701pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 153, "question": "Do you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 154, "answer": "I know it's -- it's extraordinary.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110701pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "``", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "''", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 163, "question": "But how does a melody for something like \"Phantom\" come to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "``", "NNP", "''", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 164, "answer": "Well, \"The Phantom of the Opera,\" I'm a melodist, but I'm also a theater animal.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jim Sharman"]}, "docId": "110701pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ":", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 179, "question": "Where does this music come from?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 180, "answer": "Well, I -- to finish the story, Jim Sharman said, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110701pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "``", "DT", "NNP", ",", "''", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "VBN", "RP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ":", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", ":"], "qSentId": 197, "question": "How do you come up with each song?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 198, "answer": "Well, \"The Phantom,\" I mean, originally started off, I mean for -- the phrase, I mean the -", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110701pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "RB", "DT", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 244, "question": "So, it doesn't really matter then, does it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VB", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 245, "answer": "Clearly, you can see it does, but I think that's just a very, very one-off example.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110701pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 268, "question": "When you say it just comes, I mean, can you literally get almost the whole thing in your head like that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 269, "answer": "Sometimes it'll come like that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110701pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 329, "question": "Is that true?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 330, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110701pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 344, "question": "Which of all your -- I know it's a bit like asking you for your favorite child, but which of all the musicals is your personal favorite, of yours?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "IN", "DT", "PRP$", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "WDT", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 345, "answer": "Ooh.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110701pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 368, "question": "Is it true Michael Jackson wanted to play the Phantom?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 369, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael Jackson"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110701pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 374, "question": "And did you speak to him about it, seriously?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 375, "answer": "Yes, yes I did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110701pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 380, "question": "He would've been incredible, wouldn't he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "JJ", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 381, "answer": "Well, I think he would.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110701pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 384, "question": "Wanted to play the Phantom?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 385, "answer": "He wanted to play the Phantom.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110701pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 399, "question": "If you could relive one moment live again that you've experienced, of all these shows, all the opening nights and everything, which one sticks most in your memory?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CD", "NN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", ",", "DT", "DT", "VBG", "NNS", "CC", "NN", ",", "WDT", "CD", "NNS", "JJS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 400, "answer": "It's difficult, really.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110701pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "POS", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 405, "question": "What were you thinking?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 406, "answer": "I did think that that's fairly extraordinary.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110701pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 420, "question": "Do women find, do you think, musical genius sexy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNS", "VB", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", ",", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 421, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110701pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 426, "question": "Anyone that can just conjure up these kinds of melodies, which then become anthems all around the world, that's genius, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", ",", "WDT", "RB", "VBP", "NNS", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "POS", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 427, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["McCartney"]}, "docId": "110701pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 440, "question": "Do you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 441, "answer": "I think some of McCartney's melodies are just sublime.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Britain"]}, "docId": "110701pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 467, "question": "How do you work out what you think will catch on for a morning audience?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 468, "answer": "Well, I've been doing these TV casting series back in Britain.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110701pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 482, "question": "That's very exciting, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 483, "answer": "It's been good fun.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110701pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 486, "question": "Is it one of those situations?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 487, "answer": "Well, I don't know, because we're in constant touch at the moment.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ricky Martin"]}, "docId": "110701pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 499, "question": "Any idea who may be starring in this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 500, "answer": "Well, I'm told that Ricky Martin is playing Che.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Daer"]}, "docId": "110701pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBN", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ":", ",", "CC", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 506, "question": "Are they cutting out the problem, do you think, here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "RP", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 507, "answer": "I'm beginning to think that it's off to the village I live in called Daer (ph), and early retirement.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110701pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 513, "question": "You don't have a mobile phone, cell phone?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 514, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110701pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 520, "question": "Saying what?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 521, "answer": "I can't remember now exactly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110701pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 525, "question": "Can you use the iPad?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 526, "answer": "Well, it doesn't work.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110701pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 535, "question": "Could it be you that's the problem and not the iPad?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 536, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110701pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 543, "question": "Was this actually you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 544, "answer": "This has to do with the iPad.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110701pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 562, "question": "If you were casting the all time dream musical, who would you want standing on that stage?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "DT", "NN", "NN", "JJ", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 563, "answer": "Elvis.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110701pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJS", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 576, "question": "What's been the most surreal, kind of pinch me moment you've experienced, do you think, for you personally?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", ",", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 577, "answer": "Most surreal.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110701pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 599, "question": "You played and he sang?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 600, "answer": "I think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110701pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", ",", "NN", "VB", "RB", "VB", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 639, "question": "What were you actually feeling when you came out?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 640, "answer": "I was actually feeling, please do not mess up.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110701pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 644, "question": "Because you don't have the voice of a normal -- how old are you now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ":", "WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 645, "answer": "I just turned 11.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110701pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 647, "question": "Where do you think this voice comes from?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 648, "answer": "I believe that it comes from God.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110701pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 652, "question": "How does Jackie rank, given her age, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "NNP", "NN", ",", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 653, "answer": "You know, to say that she is at the top of the heap would be an understatement.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jackie"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110701pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 671, "question": "You find all this quite funny, don't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 672, "answer": "Yeah, I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110701pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 686, "question": "What's your life like?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 687, "answer": "My life is kind of a back and forth thing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Andrea Bocelli"]}, "docId": "110701pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "RB", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 696, "question": "How far could Jackie go, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "MD", "VB", "VB", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 697, "answer": "The truth of the matter is she could go either direction in terms of pop or opera, because she has a great understanding of both, not unlike Andrea Bocelli.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jackie"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110701pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "RBR", "JJ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 703, "question": "Do you ever get nervous now or not?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "RB", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 704, "answer": "I get a lot more nervous -- I do get nervous.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110701pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 711, "question": "These are going to be tracks from your new album, is that right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 712, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110701pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "VBN", "``", "NNP", "''", "."], "qSentId": 723, "question": "Jackie, what are you going to sing for me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 724, "answer": "I'm going to be singing a song called \"Angel\".", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]